Isn't there anyone at home?
家里没有人吗?
I'll knock again, Helen.
Helen,我再敲一次.
Everything's very quiet.
毫无动静.
I'm sure there's no one at home.
我肯定家里没有人.
But that's impossible.
但那是不可能的.
Carol and Tom invited us to lunch.
Carol和Tom请我们来吃午饭.
Look through the window.
从窗子往里看看.
Can you see anything?
你能看见什么吗?
Nothing at all.
什么也看不见.
Let's try the back door.
让我们到后门去试试.
Look! Everyone's in the garden.
瞧!大家都在花园里.
Hello, Helen. Hello, Jim.
你好,Helen.你好,Jim.
Everybody wants to have lunch in the garden.
大家都想在花园里吃午饭.
It's nice and warm out here.
这外面又好又暖和.
Come and have something to drink.
来喝点东西吧.
Thanks, Carol.
谢谢,Carol.
May I have a glass of beer please?
给我一杯啤酒好吗?
Beer? There's none left.
啤酒?一点都不剩了.
You can have some lemonade.
你可以喝点柠檬水.
Lemonade!
柠檬水!
Don't believe her, Jim.
Jim,别信她的.
She's only joking.
她只是在开玩笑.
Have some beer!
喝点啤酒吧!